{
    "subject": "resource/Disco_2000_(song)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "\"Disco 2000\" is a hit single by British band Pulp, released in 1995. It reached No. 7 in the UK Singles Chart. It was the third single from the album Different Class, following \"Common People\" and the double A-side \"Mis-Shapes\"/\"Sorted for E's & Wizz\", both of which reached No. 2.The song tells the story of a narrator falling for a childhood friend called Deborah, who is more popular than he is and wondering what it would be like to meet again when they are older.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about 'Disco 2000' is that it's a hit single by British band Pulp, released in 1995. It reached No. 7 in the UK Singles Chart. It was the third single from the album Different Class, following 'Common People' and the double A-side 'Mis-Shapes'/Sorted for E'& Wizz', both of which reached No. 2. The song tells the story of a narrator falling for a childhood friend called Deborah, who is more popular than he is and wondering what it would be like to meet again when they are older.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8873080611228943,
            "question": "Who is the British band behind the hit single 'Disco 2000'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.877241313457489,
            "question": "Who is the childhood friend that the narrator in 'Disco 2000' falls for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7996236085891724,
            "question": "What does the narrator wonder about regarding his childhood friend in 'Disco 2000'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7979365587234497,
            "question": "What does the song 'Disco 2000' tell a story about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7722098231315613,
            "question": "What was the peak position of 'Disco 2000' on the UK Singles Chart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7507572770118713,
            "question": "In what year was 'Disco 2000' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7378687262535095,
            "question": "Is the narrator more or less popular than his love interest in the song 'Disco 2000'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7110340595245361,
            "question": "Which album is 'Disco 2000' featured on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6868653893470764,
            "question": "Describe the main theme of the song 'Disco 2000'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.598401665687561,
            "question": "Name the two previous singles released from the album 'Different Class'."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about 'Disco 2000' is that it's a hit single by British band Pulp, released in 1995. It reached No. 7 in the UK Singles Chart. It was the third single from the album Different Class, following 'Common People' and the double A-side 'Mis-Shapes'/Sorted for E'& Wizz', both of which reached No. 2. The song tells the story of a narrator falling for a childhood friend called Deborah, who is more popular than he is and wondering what it would be like to meet again when they are older.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1642_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the main theme of the song 'Disco 2000'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1642_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which album is 'Disco 2000' featured on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1642_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the narrator more or less popular than his love interest in the song 'Disco 2000'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1642_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1642_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate any other triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents support the fact that \"Disco 2000\" by British band Pulp, released in 1995, tells the story of a narrator falling for a childhood friend called Deborah."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided information in the documents supports all aspects of the statement. It confirms that \"Disco 2000\" is a hit single by British band Pulp, released in 1995, reached No. 7 on the UK Singles Chart, was from their album \"Different Class,\" and tells the story of the narrator falling for his childhood friend Deborah."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}